Guide to the Social Service Employees Union Records WAG.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files, 1944-2006
  - Correspondence: Cucinotta, Dominick (Treasurer then Chairman, Workload Committee), 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence: Ensley, Charles (President), 1980s (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Ensley, Charles (President), 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Ensley, Charles (President), 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Garcia, Benny (Grievance Representative and Executive Vice-President, includes materials for his obituary in 1991), 1982-1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: General, 1962-1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: General, 1970-1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Gorelick, Sol, 1965-1972, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Health Issues, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Hill, Stanley (Vice-President then President), 1968, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Hill, Stanley at AFSCME, DC 37 (Associate then Executive Director), 1985-1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Hughes, Louis (Vice-President Legislation and Political Action), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Jorge, Julie (Secretary-Treasurer), 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Kahan, Judith (Corresponding Secretary), 1965-1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Keepnews, Lew [Lou Keepnuus?] (Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee, CIO), 1952 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Knight, Patrick ( Secretary-Treasurer), 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Knight, Patrick (President), 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Lahab, Ishmael (Acting President), 1965 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Legal, 1965-1969 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Legal, 1970-1977 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Legal, 1987, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Leibowitz, Stuart (Research Director then Vice-President of Negotiations and Research), 1969, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Local 371 Office Rental and Bonds, 1966-1969, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Mage, Judith (3rd Vice-President then President), 1964-1966 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Mage, Judith (President), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Mage, Judith (President and after), 1968, 1971-1994 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Manpower, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: McKeon, James (Secretary-Treasurer), 1967-1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Members' Resignations, 1959-1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Miller, Chuck (Delegate, Crotona; Campaign Manager, Reunification Slate), 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Moore, Faryce (Vice-President Grievances and Legal Services), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Morgenstern, Martin (National Coordinator then President), 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Morgenstern, Martin (President), 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Padwee, Michael, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Perlmutter, Edward (Treasurer and Legislation Representative), 1966-1970 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Petrocelli, Frank (President), 1952-1960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Petrocelli, Frank (President), 1961-1963 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Pfefferman, Robert (Assistant to the President), 1972-1977 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Phillips, Leslie (Executive Assistant to the President then Executive Director), 1965-1972 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Philpotts, Guy (Treasurer), 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Pilson, Judith (Assistant Administrator), 1977, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Pinkett, Mary (President), 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Power, John (President), 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Quine, Gus and Patrick Quinn (Delegates to the Executive Board), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Rabinowitz, Bobbie (Vice-President of Publicity and Community Relations), 1981-1993 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Release Time, 1965-1968 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Rogoff, Joseph (President), 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Rosenblum, Herbert (Chairman, Plan Management Committee), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Schleicher, Linda, 1966-1995 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Selby, Bertha (Vice-President), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Sperling, Joseph (Vice-President Organization then President), 1972-1982 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Talbutt, John (Assistant to the President), 1990-1996 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Tambeau, William (Chairman, Social Services Committee then Community Organizer), 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Tax Exempt Status, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Tepedino, Joseph (President), 1963-1967 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Viani, Alan (President), 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Viani, Alan (President), 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Whitbeck, David (Treasurer then Education Director), 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Council of Senior Centers and Services of New York City, Inc., 1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - County of Los Angeles Department of Children's Services, 1990s (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Day Care: Correspondence, Committee, Proposals Regarding, 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Delegate Assembly, [1970s?] (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Delegate Training, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Delegate Training Conference: Leadership for the Nineties, Oct 5, 1990-Oct 7, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Delegate Training Retreat Performance: Vinie Burrows in Homemade Love, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - District Council (DC) 37: Correspondence, 1963-1996 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - District Council (DC) 37: Full-Time Employee Benefit Booklet, Undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - District Council (DC) 37: Media Overview, Jun 25, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - District Council (DC) 37 Scandal: Clippings, Correspondence and Related Material-Includes the Contract Ratification Vote that Prompted the Fraud Investigation, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - District Council (DC) 37 Scandal: Clippings, Correspondence and Related Material, May 1998-Oct 1998 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - District Council (DC) 37 Scandal: Clippings, Correspondence and Related Material-Includes Class Action Complaint Jury Demand for Mark Rosenthal and Ray Markey et al v. Rudolph Giuliani as Mayor of the City of New York et al, Nov 1998 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - District Council (DC) 37 Scandal: Clippings, Correspondence and Related Material, Dec 1998 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - District Council (DC) 37 Scandal: Clippings, Correspondence and Related Material-Includes Ethical Practices Code Amendment, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - District Council (DC) 37 Scandal: Clippings, Correspondence and Related Material-Includes the Audit Report on the Financial and Operating Practices of DC 37's Health and Security Plan Trust July 1, 1996-June 30, 1997 dated June 12, 2000, 2000, May 2001 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - District Council (DC) 37 Scandal: Ensley for Vice President of AFSCME DC 37 Campaign, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - District Council (DC) 37 Scandal: How We Built a Great Union Booklet and [Draft?] Constitution, Undated, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - District Council (DC) 37 Scandal: Media Overview Prepared for DC 37 Executive Board by the DC 37 Communications Department, Apr 11, 1999-May 13, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - District Council (DC) 37 Scandal: Report on the Ratification Vote on the 1995 Economic Agreement, Prepared by Kroll Associates, Sep 30, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Division of Post Institutional Services (DOPIS), 1982, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Dues Increase, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Early Years: Correspondence, Notices and Related Materials, 1940s-1950s (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Education and Training Opportunities, 1963-1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Educational Fund: General, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Educational Fund: General, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Educational Fund: General, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Educational Fund: General, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Educational Fund: General, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Educational Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees Meetings, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Elections, Undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Elections, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Elections, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Elections, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Elections, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Elections, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Elections, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Elections, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Elections, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Elections, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Elections, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Elections, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Elections, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Elections, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Elections, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Elections, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Elections, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Elections, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Elections, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Elections, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Elections, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Elections, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Elections, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Elections, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Elections, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Elections, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Elections, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Elections, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Elections: AFSCME Local Union Election Manual, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Elections: Certification of Results, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Emergency Assistance Unit (EAU): Memorandum on Reorganization, Jun 24, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Employment Applications and Resumes: Various Positions, 1986-1992 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - English First Initiative/Bilingualism, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Executive Board: Correspondence (form letters), 1961-1971 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Executive Board: Member Lists, 1960s, 1980s (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Executive Board: Position Paper Presented to Executive Committee by Staff Members, Jan 20, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Executive Board: Questionnaires to Prepare for Collective Bargaining (late 1960s?), Undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Executive Board: Resolutions and Recommendations, 1960s (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Executive Committee, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Expense Vouchers: General, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Expert Services Program, [1980s?] (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Family Meals at Low Cost Using Donated Foods: Booklet by U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Fasanella, Ralph: Labor Artist, 1970s-1980s (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Field Offices, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Financial Statements, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements and Related Materials, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Financial Statements and Related Materials, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Financial Statements and Related Materials, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements and Related Materials, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Financial Statements and Related Materials, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Financial Statements and Related Materials, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements and Related Materials, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Financial Statements and Related Materials, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Financial Statements, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Financial Statements and Related Materials, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Financial Statements, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Financial Statements and Related Materials, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Financial Statements, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Financial Statements, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Financial Statements, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Financial Statements, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Financial Statements, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Financial Statements, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Fire Salvage Units, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Future of Social Services in the Public Sector: Toward A More Caring System (Conference), Dec 3, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - General: Poems, Updates, Meetings and Related Materials, 1966-1989 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Gloria Richardson and the Cambridge Civil Rights Movement, 1962-1964 by Edward K. Turner, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Gotbaum, Victor: General, 1985-1978 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Grassroots Leadership Speakers, 1990s (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Health Careers Opportunity Program, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Hispanic Labor Committee, 1985-1992 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Holiday Cards, [1990?] (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Home Care: Newsday Press Clippings and Response, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Home Economists/Homemakers, 1958-1977 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Homeless: AIDS Units, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Homeless: Catherine Street Shelter, 1991, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Homeless: City of New York Continuum of Housing and Services for the Medically Frail and HIV-IU Report and Related Materials, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Homeless: Crisis Intervention Services (CIS)-Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Homeless: Crisis Intervention Services (CIS)-Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Homeless: Cruel Brinkmanship: Planning for the Homeless-1983 by the Coalition for the Homeless, Aug 16, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Homeless: Department of Homeless Services (DHS), 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Homeless: DHS, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Homeless: Department of Homeless Services (DHS), 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Homeless: DHS Issues Including Bellevue Closing, Layoffs, Council/Mayoral Conflicts and Related Materials, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Homeless: DHS Request for Proposals (RFP) "To Privatize the Intake and Assessment of Homeless and Potentially Homeless Single Adult Men Presently Entering the City's System at a Single Point", 2006 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Homeless: "Diary of a Homeless Man," New York Magazine, Feb 21, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Homeless: Establishment of DHS, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Homeless: Establishment of DHS, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Homeless: Homeless Crisis-Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Homeless: Homelessness Prevention Program, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Homeless: Kenmore Hotel Shelter, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Homeless: Memorandum of Understanding (DHS Agreement), 1999 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Homeless: Pilot Operational Guidelines-Hotel Service Program, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Homeless: Press Conference by SSEU and Related Materials, Nov 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Homeless: Resolution to Enact a Moratorium on Residential Evictions. Includes Press on Eleanor Bumpers' Case, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Homeless: Shelters-Press Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Homeless: Shelters-Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Homeless: Shelters-Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Homeless: Shelters-Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials including Committee on the Homeless, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Homeless: Shelters-Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials including Committee on the Homeless, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Homeless: Shelters-Press Clippings, 1990s (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Homeless: Shelters-Press Clippings and Related Materials, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Homeless: Shelters Security and Staffing-Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Hom Homeless: DHS eless: Homeless: Tuberculosis in Shelters-Memos, Press Clippings, Informational Materials, 1990-1994 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Homeless: Tuberculosis-Office of Staff Development and Training Infections Disease Control Agenda Materials, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Houseparents, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Housing, 1960s (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - How to Do Leaflets, Newsletters and Newspapers by Nancy Brigham, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - How to Fight the Slum Landlord, [1966?] (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Human Resources Administration, City of New York (HRA): Consolidated Services Plan Annual Implementation Reports, 1986, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - HRA: correspondence, informational bulletins and Related Materials, 1967-1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - HRA: correspondence, informational bulletins and Related Materials, 1986-1994 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - HRA: DSS/Headcount Control Document-Feb '97 revised, Apr 28, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - HRA: Non-Managerial Employee Performance Evaluation, May 23, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - HRA: Proposed Restructuring of Division of AIDS Services (DAS), Jan 3, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - HRA: Protective Services for Adults (PSA), Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials (includes Joseph Stilletto Case), 1985-1990 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - HRA: Reorganization, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - HRA: Review and Hiring of George Gross, Press Clippings, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Inequity Provision, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Child Mental Health Conference: Child Welfare Service in New York City: "Double, Double, Toil and Trouble?", Feb 7, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - International Labor Communications Association (ILCA), 1988, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Issues re: Haiti, 1985, 1990-1992, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - It's Your Welfare: City of New York Department of Welfare Booklet, Dec 1, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Labor Film Festivals, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Labor Press Council of Metropolitan New York: conference and Related Materials, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Labor Research Association, 1986-1992 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Layoff Crises: Memoranda, Petitions and Related Material including Sperling v. Department of Social Services, 1974-1977 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Leaflets, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Leaflets, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Leaflets, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Leaflets, Jan 1965-Aug 1965 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Leaflets, Undated, Sep 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Leaflets, Jan 1966-Mar 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Leaflets, Apr 1966-May 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Leaflets, Jun 1966-Aug 1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Leaflets, Sep 1966-Nov 1966 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Leaflets, Dec 1966, Dec 1966 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Leaflets, Jan 1967-Mar 1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Leaflets, Apr 1967-May 1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Leaflets, Jun 1967-Jul 1967 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Leaflets, Aug 1967-Dec 1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Leaflets, Undated, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Leaflets, Jan 1968-Jun 1968 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Leaflets, Undated, Jul 1968-Dec 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Leaflets, Jan 1969-May 1969 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Leaflets, Jun 1969-Aug 1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Leaflets, Undated, Jul 1969-Dec 1969 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Leaflets, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Leaflets, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Leaflets, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Leaflets, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Leaflets, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Leaflets, Jan 1975-May 1975 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Leaflets, Undated, Jul 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Leaflets, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Leaflets, 1977, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Leaflets: Distribution, 1969, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Leaflets: Elections, Undated, 1969-1978 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Leaflets: Union Activists including Seeds of Liberation, The Committee for Union Effectiveness (CUE), the Committee of 14, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Leaflets: Work Actions, 1969, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Leaves: Accruals and Balances, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Legal Defense Fund, 1970-1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Legal Services Fund, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Legal Services Fund, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Lists: Activists (Active Members), 1964-1969 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Lists: Activists (Active Members), 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Lists: Activists (Active Members), 1981, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Lists: General, Undated, 1969-1990s (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Lists: Jurisdiction, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Lists: MSW Graduates, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Lists: Officers, Undated, 1958, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Lists: Staff, Undated, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Lists: Telephone Directories/Lists, Undated, 1981-1992 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Lost in the Margins: Labor and the Media (a publication of FAIR), Summer 1990 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Master Sheets, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Mayor's Management Report [Edward I. Koch], Sep 17, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Mechanics of the Job: A Guide for Caseworkers(Welfare Local 371), Dec 1965 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Medical Social Workers, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Meeting Notices, Undated, 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Meeting Notices, 1974-1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Meetings with Commissioners, 1958-1960, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Member Correspondence and Complaints, 1973-1986 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Member Information and Related Materials, 1964-1992 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Members for a Militant Caucus, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Memoranda, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Memoranda, 1970-1974 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Memoranda, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Memoranda, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda, Jan 1977-Jun 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda, Jul 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda, 1982-1989 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda, 1990s (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Memorandum: Supervision of Employee Attendance and Punctuality, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Merger Agreement: Local 371 and SSEU (original with signatures), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Merger of SSEU and Local 371: Flyers and Related Materials Against, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Merger of SSEU and Local 371: Flyers and Related Materials in Favor, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Merger of SSEU and Local 371: General, including Affiliations Committee materials, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Budget Package, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - MLC: Memorandum of Economic Agreement, Jul 15, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 14)